Guide to the Annina Nosei Gallery Archive 1963-2009 MSS.298
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Jean-Michel Basquiat Artist File, 1981-2003; 200737
  - Subseries F: Visuals Binders, 205263
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book I [3/3], undated; 208997 (Album BM)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [1/3], undated; 208998 (Album BN)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [2/3], undated; 208999 (Album BO)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [3/3], undated; 209000 (Album BP)
  - Subseries G: Material Separated from Visuals Binders, 204169
    The order of folders in this subseries follows the order of binders in Series IV, Subseries F.
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book I [Front Pocket], undated; 209280 (Box 35, Folder 72)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book I [1/3] [From Binder Sleeve 5/17], undated; 209281 (Box 35, Folder 73)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book I [3/3] [From Binder Sleeve 13/22], undated; 209282 (Box 35, Folder 74)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [Front Pocket], undated; 209289 (Box 35, Folder 75)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [3/3] [From Binder Sleeve 23/29], undated; 209283 (Box 35, Folder 76)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [3/3] [From Binder Sleeve 24/29], undated; 209284 (Box 35, Folder 77)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [Back Pocket], undated; 209285 (Box 35, Folder 78)
  - Subseries H: Polaroids, 204170
    - Basquiat Polaroids, undated; 209006 (Album BQ)
  - Subseries I: Catalogs, 204171
    - [Catalogs] [1/3], 1982, 1983; 208205 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - [Catalogs] [2/3], 1989-1996; 208206 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - [Catalogs] [3/3], undated; 208207 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Subseries J: Periodicals, Clippings, 204550
    Subseries arranged chronologically.
    - [Basquiat - Loose Clippings], 1982-1998; 208208 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - [Periodicals] [1/4], 1983; 208209 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - [Periodicals] [2/4], 1983-1988; 208210 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - [Periodicals] [3/4], 1992; 208211 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - [Periodicals] [4/4], 1997; 208212 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Series V: Exhibition Records, 1980-2009; 208482
  Series comprises materials related to each show held at the Annina Nosei Gallery. Materials include installation photographs, price lists, artist bios, exhibition cards, press clippings, catalogs, and guest books.
  Exhibition Records: Subseries A-G comprise what the gallery termed "Exhibition Records," a term denoting all materials produced and collected in connection with a specific exhibition. These records were originally sleeved in binders. Material has been removed from binder sleeves and binders and placed in folders and boxes. Titles of binders have been retained in the titles of subseries.
  Materials in these subseries are arranged in the order in which they were filed in their original binders, which is reverse chronological order for each binder. The binders (subseries) themselves have been ordered chronologically by the archivist.
  Each folder represents a specific exhibition (e.g., all of the material relating to the Barbara Kruger March 5-26, 1983 show is put into one folder), regardless of how many binder sleeves the material orignally occupied. Most binders were accompanied by a list of binder contents listing the exhibitions included in the date range for that binder. These lists, where available, were used by the archivist to create folder titles. Where these lists were absent, the archivist has supplied folder titles by referring to the chronological lists found in the yearly catalogs for the gallery.
  Some consecutive exhibitions are represented by very little material. In such a case, that material is placed in a single folder, which is labelled with the artists' names and show titles separated by semicolons (e.g., "[Stephen Mueller; Keith Milow; Group Show; Keith Haring]").
  Catalogs: Subseries H comprises catalogs created by the gallery to accompany each exhibition.
  Guest Books: Subseries I comprises guest books signed by gallery patrons.
  - Subseries A: Annina Nosei Gallery Shows; 1982-1983, 1983-1984, 208513
    - [Front Pocket], undated; 208521 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - [Summer Group Show], 1984; 208522 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - [Helmut Middendorf], 1984; 208523 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - [Group Show; Apr 14 - May 4 1984], 208524 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - [David Bowes "Drawings"], 1984; 208525 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - [Barbara Kruger], 1984; 208526 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - [David Bowes "Capriccios"], 1984; 208527 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - [Sabina Mirri], 1984; 208528 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - [European Expressions], 1983; 208529 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - [Group Show; Nov 5, 1983], 208530 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - [Ira Richer], 1983; 208531 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - [Group Show; June 11 - July 29, 1983], 208532 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - [K.H. Hodicke], 1983; 208533 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - [Athos Ongaro], 1983; 208534 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - [Francois Boisrond], 1983; 208535 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - [Barbara Kruger], 1983; 208536 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - [Kenny Scharf], 1983; 208537 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - [Mario Schifano], 1983; 208538 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - [Selected Works; Dec 16 - Jan 6, 1983], 208539 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - [Jean-Michel Basquiat], 1982; 208540 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - [Stephen Mueller; Keith Milow; Group Show; Keith Haring], 1981, 1982; 208541 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - [David Deutsch], 1981; 208542 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - [Group Show; March 1981], 208543 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - [Kim Gordon at White Columns], undated; 208544 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - [Drawings & Paintings on Paper], 1980; 208545 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - [American and Italian New Image Artists], 1981; 208546 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - [Mimmo Paladino], 1980; 208547 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - [Initial Group Show; May - June 1980], 208548 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - [Unlabelled Polaroids from Binder Sleeve of Pre-gallery Curating], undated; 208549 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - [Annina Nosei Pre-gallery Curating], undated; 208550 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - [Back Pocket], 1980, 1981; 208551 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Subseries B: Annina Nosei Gallery Shows; September 1984 - August 1986, 208514
    - [Front Pocket, including List of Binder Contents], 1986, 1995; 208552 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - [Group Show], 1986; 208553 (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - [Pietro Fortuna], 1986; 208554 (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - [Pizzi Cannella], 1986; 208555 (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - [Claudio Palmieri], 1986; 208556 (Box 48, Folder 36)
    - [Barbara Kruger], 1986; 208557 (Box 48, Folder 37)
    - [Helmut Middendorf], 1986; 208558 (Box 48, Folder 38)
    - [Basquiat "Paintings from 1982"], 1986; 208559 (Box 48, Folder 39)
    - [Chuck Connelly], 1985; 208560 (Box 48, Folder 40)
    - [Vincent Gallo], 1985; 208561 (Box 48, Folder 41)
    - ["Drawing the Line - Painting"], 1985; 208562 (Box 48, Folder 42)
    - ["The Door"], 1985; 208563 (Box 48, Folder 43)
    - [Sabina Mirri], 1985; 208564 (Box 48, Folder 44)
    - [Francois Boisrond], 1985; 208565 (Box 48, Folder 45)
    - [Ira Richer], 1985; 208566 (Box 48, Folder 46)
    - [Nunzio], 1985; 208567 (Box 48, Folder 47)
    - [Pizzi Cannella], 1985; 208568 (Box 48, Folder 48)
    - [Marco Tirelli], 1985; 208569 (Box 48, Folder 49)
    - [Stephen Mueller], 1984; 208570 (Box 48, Folder 50)
    - [Karel Appel], 1984; 208571 (Box 48, Folder 51)
    - [Chuck Connelly], 1984; 208572 (Box 48, Folder 52)
    - [Georges Rousse], 1984; 208573 (Box 48, Folder 53)
  - Subseries C: Annina Nosei Gallery Shows; October 1986 to December 1989 (included [sic], 204172
    - [List of Binder Contents], undated; 208574 (Box 48, Folder 54)
    - [Mary Obering], 208575 (Box 48, Folder 55)
    - [Works on Paper], 1989; 208576 (Box 48, Folder 56)
    - [Ronald Gault Jirado], 1989; 208577 (Box 48, Folder 57)
    - [Group Show], 1989; 208578 (Box 48, Folder 58)
    - [Group Exhibition to Benefit the AIDS Crisis], 1989; 208579 (Box 48, Folder 59)
    - [Christiane Richter], 1989; 208580 (Box 48, Folder 60)
    - [Beth Brenner], 1989; 208581 (Box 48, Folder 61)
    - [Gary Lang], 1989; 208582 (Box 48, Folder 62)
    - [Julio Galan], 1989; 208583 (Box 48, Folder 63)
    - [ARCO], 1989; 208584 (Box 48, Folder 64)
    - [Ellen Brooks], 1989; 208585 (Box 48, Folder 65)
    - [Helmut Middendorf], 1989; 208586 (Box 48, Folder 66)
    - [Jean-Michel Basquiat Memorial Exhibition], 1988; 208587 (Box 48, Folder 67)
    - [Stephen Mueller], 1989; 208588 (Box 48, Folder 68)
    - ["Metathesis"], 1988; 208589 (Box 48, Folder 69)
    - [Vincent Gallo], 1988; 208590 (Box 48, Folder 70)
    - ["Mutations"], 1988; 208591 (Box 48, Folder 71)
    - [Mary Oberling], 1988; 208592 (Box 48, Folder 72)
    - [Group Show], 1988; 208593 (Box 48, Folder 73)
    - [Alan McCollum], 1988; 208594 (Box 48, Folder 74)
    - [Vincent Gallo], 1988; 208595 (Box 48, Folder 75)
    - ["Fragments"], 1988; 208596 (Box 48, Folder 76)
    - [Ellen Brooks], 1987; 208597 (Box 48, Folder 77)
    - [Beth Brenner], 1987; 208598 (Box 48, Folder 78)
    - [Rotating Photography], 1987; 208599 (Box 48, Folder 79)
    - ["Spatial-FX"], 1987; 208600 (Box 48, Folder 80)
    - [Chuck Connelly], 1987; 208601 (Box 48, Folder 81)
    - [Andy Moses], 1987; 208602 (Box 48, Folder 82)
    - [Tod Wizon], 1987; 208603 (Box 48, Folder 83)
    - [Nunzio], 1987; 208604 (Box 48, Folder 84)
    - [Group Show], 1987; 208605 (Box 48, Folder 85)
    - [Ira Richer], 1987; 208606 (Box 48, Folder 86)
    - [Group Show], 1986; 208607 (Box 48, Folder 87)
    - [Stephen Mueller], 1986; 208608 (Box 48, Folder 88)
    - [Vincent Gallo], 1986; 208609 (Box 48, Folder 89)
  - Subseries D: Annina Nosei Gallery Shows; January 1990 - July 1992, 208518
    - [List of Binder Contents], undated; 208610 (Box 48, Folder 90)
    - [Specs Photography], 1992; 208611 (Box 48, Folder 91)
    - [Stephen Mueller], 1992; 208612 (Box 48, Folder 92)
    - [Julio Galan], 1992; 208613 (Box 48, Folder 93)
    - [Sal Scarpitta], 1992; 208614 (Box 48, Folder 94)
    - [Works on Paper], 1991; 208615 (Box 48, Folder 95)
    - [Cheri Samba], 1991; 208616 (Box 48, Folder 96)
    - [Jenny Watson], 1991; 208617 (Box 48, Folder 97)
    - [Gian Marco Montesano], 1991; 208618 (Box 48, Folder 98)
    - [Internationale Contemporanea], 1991; 208619 (Box 48, Folder 99)
    - [Guillermo Kuitca], 1991; 208620 (Box 48, Folder 100)
    - ["Landscape Painting"], 1991; 208621 (Box 48, Folder 101)
    - [Nancy Bowen, Gary Lang], 1991; 208622 (Box 48, Folder 102)
    - ["Personal Portraits"], 1991; 208623 (Box 48, Folder 103)
    - [Helmut Middendorf], 1991; 208624 (Box 48, Folder 104)
    - [Stephen Mueller], 1990; 208625 (Box 48, Folder 105)
    - [Tsibi Geva], 1990; 208626 (Box 48, Folder 106)
    - [Julio Galan], 1990; 208627 (Box 48, Folder 107)
    - [Cheri Samba], 1990; 208628 (Box 48, Folder 108)
    - [Gary Lang], 1990; 208629 (Box 48, Folder 110)
    - [Guillermo Kuitca], 1990; 208630 (Box 48, Folder 111)
    - [Group Show], 1990; 208631 (Box 48, Folder 112)
  - Subseries E: Exhibitions; October 1992 - Jan 1993 - 94 - 96, 208519
    - [Front Pocket, Including List of Binder Contents], undated; 208632 (Box 48, Folder 113)
    - [Helmut Middendorf; Stephen Mueller; Manuel Ocampo; Paul D. Miller], 1996, 1997; 208633 (Box 48, Folder 114)
    - [Summer Group Show Exhibition; Julio Galan; Arturo Elizondo; Ghada Amer; Danielle Galliano], 1996; 208634 (Box 48, Folder 115)
    - [Unlabelled Folder of Exhibition], undated; 208635 (Box 48, Folder 116)
    - [Athos Ongaro; Inaugural Exhibition], 1995, 1996; 208636 (Box 48, Folder 117)
    - [Shirin Neshat; Summer Invitational], 1995; 208637 (Box 48, Folder 118)
    - [Arturo Duclos; Flechmuller; Kocheisen + Hullmann; Tsibi Geva], 1995; 208638 (Box 48, Folder 119)
    - [Anna Paparatti], 1994; 208639 (Box 48, Folder 120)
    - [Cheri Samba; Teresa Serrano, 1994; 208640 (Box 48, Folder 121)
    - [Studio Annina Nosei Roma], 1994; 208641 (Box 48, Folder 122)
    - [Jenny Watson; Group Exhibition], 1994; 208691 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - [Arturo Duclos; Manuel Ocampo; Flechemuller], 1994; 208692 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - [Stephen Mueller Group Exhibition], 1993-1994; 208693 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - [Kocheisen + Hullmann; Quotes from Past Exhibitions; Nancy Bowen], 1993; 208694 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - ["Continuing Generations"], 1993; 208695 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - ["7 Latin American Artists"], 1993; 208696 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - [Tsibi Geva], 1993; 208697 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - [Arturo Duclos], 1993; 208698 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - [Pizzi Cannella], 1993; 208699 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - [Group Exhibition], 1993; 208700 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - [Jenny Watson], 1992; 208731 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - [Gian Marco Montesano], 1992; 208701 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - ["Who's Afraid of Marcel Duchamp, Minimalism and Passport Photography"], 1992; 208702 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Subseries F: Exhibitions Record; Jan 1997 - Dec 1999, 208645
    - [List of Binder Contents], undated; 208703 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - [James Aldridge; Fernando Canovas; Group Exhibition; Jose Bedia], 1999; 208704 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - [Abraham David Christian], 1999; 208705 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - [Myriam Laplante; Liliana Porter; "Filtered Components"; Vincent Gallo; Arturo Elizondo], 1998-1999; 208706 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - [Santolo de Luca], 1998; 208707 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - [Deborah Turbeville], 1998; 208708 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - [Gallery Artists; Jenny Watson; Fernando Canovas], 1998; 208732 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - [Ghada Amer], 1998; 208709 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - ["Magiciens de la Terre"], 1998; 208710 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - [Martin G. Larralde; Graciela Hasper], 1997, 1998; 208711 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - [Winter Group Exhibition], 1997; 208712 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - [Pablo Siquier], 1997; 208713 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - [Danielle Galliano], 1997; 208714 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - [Summer Group Show], 1997; 208715 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - [Fabian Burgos], 1997; 208716 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - [Shirin Neshat; Arturo Duclos], 1997; 208717 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - [Fernando Canovas; Teresa Serrano; Group Drawing Exhibition], 1997; 208718 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - [Photocopy of Back of Unidentified Studio Anna Nosei Roma Postcard], undated; 208719 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Subseries G: Exhibition Records Jan. 2000 -, 208678
    - [Front Pocket including List of Binder Contents], undated; 208720 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - [Leemour Pelli; Izumi Chiraluce], 2008, 2009; 208721 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - [Gian Marco Montesano; Myriam Laplante; "Everland"], 2008, 2009; 208722 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - [Heidi McFall; Kocheisen + Hullman; Michelle Mercurio; Tsibi Geva], 2005; 208723 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - [Lucia Warck Meister; Phillip Toledano; Arturo Elizondo; Liliana Porter; "Young Miami"], 2004; 208724 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - [Summer Group Show; Marta Maria Perez Bravo; Jenny Watson; Ieva Mediodia; Federico Uribe], 2004; 208725 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - [Frederico Uribe; James Rosenquist; Group Show; Heidi McFall; Group Exhibition], 2003; 208726 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - [Paolo W Tamburella; Federico Uribe; Summer Group Exhibition; Myriam Laplante; Heidi McFall; David Bowes; Liliana Porter], 2002; 208727 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - [Arturo Elizondo; Jose Bedia; Tsibi Geva; Summer Group Exhibition; Paolo W. Tamburella; Tristiano Di Robilant; Group Exhibition; Jenny Watson], 2001; 208733 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - [Gernot Linder, Carole Benzaken; Cemin, Christian, Schwart, Federico Uribe; Graciela Hasper; Summer Invitational; Liliana Porter], 2000; 208728 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - [Marta Maria Perez Bravo; Kocheisen + Hullmann; Fabian Burgos; Group Photography Exhibition], 1999, 2000; 208729 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - [Back Pocket], 2000; 208730 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - Subseries H: Catalogs, 204173
    Subseries comprises catalogs of artists and artists' works produced regularly by the Annina Nosei Gallery. Catalogs come in the following categories: Individual Artists, "Group Shows," "7 Latin American Artists," "The Door," and Occasional Compilations of exhibitions over a span of three to five years, each of which is described as "a testimony recording a seletion of the artist I have worked with during the last three [or "five"] years."
    Subseries is arranged chronologically by year and alphabetically within the same year.
    - Group Shows, 1983-1985; 208213 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Chuck Connelly, 1985; 208216 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - The Door, 1985; 208215 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Vincent Gallo, 1985; 208214 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Claudio Palmeri, 1986; 208217 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - [Occasional Compilations] [1/2], 1986-1998; 208218 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - [Occasional Compilations] [2/2], 1998-2006; 208219 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Beth Brenner, 1987; 208220 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Helmut Middendorf, 1990; 208221 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Tsibi Geva, 1990; 208222 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Julio Galan, 1990-1996; 208223 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Jenny Watson, 1991; 208224 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Gian Marco Montesano, 1991, 1992; 208225 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - 7 Latin American Artists, 1993; 208226 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Teresa Serrano, 1994; 208227 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Stephen Mueller, 1996; 208228 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Shirin Neshat, 1997; 208229 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Myriam Leplante, 1999; 208230 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Arturo Elizondo, 2001; 208231 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Heidi McFall [1/2], 2002-2005; 208232 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Heidi McFall [2/2], 2008; 208233 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Subseries I: Guest Books, 204174
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [1], 1994; 208234 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [2], 1994, 1995; 208235 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [3], 1995, 1996; 208236 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [4], 1996, 1997; 208237 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [5], 1997; 208238 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [6], 1997; 208239 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - [Spiral-Bound Guestbook] [1], 1997, 1998; 208240 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - [Spiral-Bound Guestbook] [2], 1998; 208241 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - [Loose Paper from "Spiral-Bound Guestbook [2]"], 1998; 208243 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - [Spiral-Bbound Guestbook] [3], 1998; 208245 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [7], 1998, 1999; 208246 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Series VI: Other Administrative Files, 1978-2009; 208484
  Series comprises material related to the general day-to-day administration of the gallery itself and the gallery space.
  - Subseries A: Planners, 200739
    Subseries is arranged chronologically. Interleaved material photocopied to indicated original location. Original and photocopy are placed in back of folder.
    - [1978, 1988 Planner], 208247 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - [1982 Planner], 208248 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - [1989, 1991 Planner], 208249 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - [1993 Planner], 208250 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - [2005 Planner], 208251 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Memos, 200740
    - Memos [Apr 28, 1998 - Jun9, 1998], 208252 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Memos [Jun 19, 1998 - Aug 7, 1998], 208253 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Memos [Sept 2, 1998 - Dec 17, 1998], 208254 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Memos [Jan 15, 1999 - May 27, 1999], 208255 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Memos [June 29, 1999 - Oct 10, 1999], 208256 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Memos [Oct 19, 1999 - Dec 21, 1999], 208258 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Memos [Jan 4, 2000 - Mar 28, 2000], 208259 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Memos [Apr 4, 2000 - May 16, 2000], 208260 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Memos [May 30, 2000 - Sept 26, 2000], 208261 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Memos [Oct 17, 2000 - Dec. 12, 2000], 208262 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Memos [Jan 2, 2001 - Mar 26, 2001], 208263 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Memos [Mar 27, 2001 - May 8, 2001], 208264 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Memos [Jul 2, 2001 - Oct 11, 2001], 208265 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Memos [Oct 30, 2001 - Dec 11, 2001], 208266 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Memos [Jan 8, 2002 - Apr 9, 2002], 208267 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Memos [Apr 30, 2002 - Sep 17, 2002], 208268 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Memos [Oct 1, 2002 - Dec 17, 2002], 208269 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Memos [Jan 8, 2003 - Nov 28, 2003], 208270 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Memos [Jan 7, 2004 - Mar 2, 2004], 208271 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Memos [March 9, 2004 - June 1, 2004], 208272 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Memos [June 14, 2004 - Dec 21, 2004], 208273 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Memos [Jan 5, 2005 - May 10, 2005], 208274 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Memos [May 24, 2005 - Oct 4, 2005], 208275 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Memos [Oct 6, 2005 - Dec 19, 2005], 208276 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Memos [Jan 12, 2006 - Oct 23, 2006; Mar 5, 2007 - July 12, 2007], 2006, 2007; 208277 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Memos [June 26, 2008 - Jan 12, 2009], 2008, 2009; 208278 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Memos [Fax from Lee Ortega to Mitchell Langsner], undated; 208279 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Memos [Exhibition Cards for Jenny Watson, Helmut Middendorf, Patrick Grant], 1990, 1991, 2000; 208280 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Subseries C: Gallery Space, 210039
    - Fire 88', 1988; 207706 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      Folder contains documents and photographs relating to a 1988 fire at the gallery. It was originally filed at the end of Series II, Subseries E, and remains physically in its original place (box 23, folder 9).
- Series VII: Pre-gallery Curating, 1977-1978; 206161
  Before opening her own gallery, Annina Nosei curated exhibitions at various locations. Series comprises material drawn from the exhibitions "Discussions," "Painting," "Memory," "Angelo Savelli: Paintings & Sculpture," and comprises press releases, programs, brochures, artist bios, and an essay by Annina Nosei on Savelli.
  - Pre-Gallery Curating, 1977-1978; 210034 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Series VIII: Misc. Periodicals and Clippings, undated; 200741
  Materials were originally grouped by artist and shelved in magazine files bearing the artist's name. That grouping is preserved, and the folder titles bear the original labels of the magazine files.
  The folder "Jose Bedia [/Guillermo Kuitca]" contains material related to both Bedia and Kuitca though the original folder only listed Bedia's name.
  Series comprises some monographs of artists represented by the gallery, some periodicals that include artists represented by the gallery, and various clippings, all accumulated and stored by the gallery.
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated; 208281 (Box 39)
    Fabian Burgos, Graciela Hasper, Tsibi Geva, Julio Galan, Jose Bedia, Guillermo Kuitca
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated; 208282 (Box 40)
    Jose Bedia, Guillermo Kuitca, Arturo Elizando, Kocheisen + Hullman, Myriam Laplant, Jenny Watson, David Bowes, Helmut Middendorf
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated; 208283 (Box 41)
    Shirin Neshat, Liliana Porter, Salomé, Bernd Koberling, Arturo Duclos, Manuel Ocampo
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated; 208284 (Box 42)
    Liliana Porter, Jenny Watson, Karel Appel, David Bowes, Nancy Bowen, Keith Milow, David Deutsch, Pierre and Giles, Colombo
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated; 208285 (Box 43)
    Daniele Galliano, Sabina Mirri, Marco Montesano, Mimmo Paladino, Cheri Samba
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated; 208286 (Box 44)
    Ellen Brooks, Pizzi Cannella, De Luca, Gilardi, Commandeur, Welch, Amer, Ongaro, David Bowes, Gallo, Schuyff, Varejao, Paparatti, Chuck Connelly, Palmieri, Marco Tirelli, Nunzio
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated; 208287 (Box 45)